http://www.mybambino.com/pages/securityandprivacy

SALE
Close outs!
SALE
Close outs!
Security Policy
MyBambino appreciates your patronage and respects your privacy. Any information that you provide to us is used only to process your order(s), reply to your questions, and to improve your future experiences with our website. We will not share. rent or sell your personal information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, or credit card information, with anyone for any reason, unless required to by law.
MyBambino uses technology called Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt any personal information you transmit to us online.
The information is encrypted on your computer and decoded after it reaches MyBambino's secure server. This information cannot be decrypted during transit. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, you cannot be held liable for more than $50.00 of unauthorized charges on your card.
Shopping online at MyBambino is statistically safer than using your credit card at a restaurant or department store. Technical experts point out that online purchases without human intervention are far safer than traditional credit card transactions because the information is immediately encrypted into a scrambled message that can only be decrypted by an authorized computer.
If you are still nervous about ordering online, we can take your order by phone. Call us at 800-927-0707 or mail us at office@mybambino.com with your number and best time to call back.
What personal information we collect and why?
We collect personal information primarily so that we may process your order, but also so that we may personalize your purchases and make your shopping experience as unique as possible. In addition to personal information collected for purposes of processing your order, we may ask for the following information:
Billing and Shipping InformationDuring the checkout process, we ask for certain personal information - name, address, e-mail, telephone number and credit card information - all of which are necessary for us to process your order and ship it to you. Basic personal information such as name, address and telephone number, but not credit card numbers, may be transmitted to contracted third parties (UPS, FedEx, etc.) solely for the purpose of shipping your order. As described above, ordering with MyBambino is safe and secure because we use Secure Socket Layer Technology which encrypts the information you send to us. This information cannot be decrypted during transmission and is decoded on MyBambino's secure server, which cannot be accessed by 3rd parties. MyBambino may also use this information to send you our printed catalog or other announcements via postal mail.
Personalization InformationIn order to hand-personalize each product, MyBambino requires that you submit certain private information to us for most items. This may consist of your child's name(s) or age(s), birthdate(s), etc. This information is used only to personalize your purchases and is held strictly confidential.
E-mail Addresses
During the checkout process, we collect your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is used only so that you may receive offers and announcements via e-mail from MyBambino, and is not forwarded to any third parties. At any time, you may modify your information by sending an e-mail to office@mybambino.com.
Cookies
MyBambino uses a feature of your Internet web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer.
Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive.
MyBambino creates and then uses these cookie files to track your cart contents and to recognize you when you return to MyBambino's site.
This saves you from having to re-input your billing and shipping information the next time you shop with us.
Cookies cannot be used by MyBambino to retrieve any personal information about you unless you have previously purchased from MyBambino.
MyBambino does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you.
In some instances, your browser may have been set to not accept cookies.
If so, you will see a message when the MyBambino web site tries to access any cookies.
By default, most all browsers are setup to accept cookies when first installed.
If your is not, you can change your cookie settings usually in the "Security Options" or "Preferences" section of your browser (or something similar).
